

# **NASSER ALHASHASH**

nasseralhashash@gmail.com | 966583044322 | AlRiyadh

### **Summary**

Experienced communications professional successful at writing, proofreading and enhancing materials to promote messages, improve perception or enable change. Tactical planner and decisive leader with excellent problem-solving, conflict management and program oversight skills. Building and strengthening relationships with members of the media.

#### Skills

- Articulate communication skills
- Creating strategies through the use of social media
- Team leadership skills
- Research abilities
- creative writing

- Negotiation skill
- Complete tasks as required and on time
- Editing and proofreading
- Using social media in the internal communication process, focusing on quality and speed
- Dealing skill and flexibility with others

### Experience

Deanship of Student Affairs for Student Activities and Partnership | Riyadh Internal Communication Officer 01/2018 - 01/2020

- Worked for two consecutive years at the Deanship of Student Affairs for student activities and partnership. The most important tasks assigned to me during this period are to enhance the environment of internal communication between students by increasing the number of activities within the university, in addition to increasing the number of professional courses that benefit male and female students at the university and in the labor market after the university.
- Ensuring to increase student activities for non-Saudi students
- Managed website copy and social media profiles and pages.
- Wrote and edited content to create consistent and positive image.
- Alkayan Group | Riyadh **Branch Operations Supervisor** 03/2019 - 06/2019
- It is a diverse group interested in investing in investing in the field of food and beverages.
- Managed and inspired team members to perform to full potential, driving branch profitability.
- Built strong rapport with new and existing clients to better serve financial needs and promote branch loyalty.
- Planned work schedules to maintain adequate staffing levels.
- Opening channels for employees and discussing human resource management
- Alkayan Group | Riyadh

  Internal Communication Specialist

07/2019 - 07/2022

- Created original content for blog posts and website articles.
- Collaborated with graphic design and marketing teams to devise effective branding strategies.
- Drafted social media posts and created videos with eye for viral content strategies.
- Ensure organizationals initiatives and projects are successfully communicated to employees and stakeholders

- Plan, edit and write content for a variety of internal communications channels
- Use social media to communicate with staff internally
- Assist in delivering presentations at organizational events
- Respond to internal feedback and adjust communications content accordingly
- I approached the Communications and Outreach team with several advertising agencies to help write content

Trainee

03/2023 - Current

- Saudi Research and Media Group | Riyadh Attended training sessions and meetings to learn new information and develop personal skills.
  - Developed essential skills and techniques through diligent practice.
  - Worked alongside senior team members to learn related job tasks and roles.

### **Education and Training**

King Saud University | Riyadh Bachelor of Arts in Public Relations, Communication And Media Studies Expected in 06/2023

Lang	gua	ges
------	-----	-----

**Arabic:** First Language **English:** 

Advanced

## **Projects**

Media and advertising campaign's for the electric car agency - Lucidia

• I planned a virtual media campaign with the aim of informing the masses interested in electric cars The media campaign includes informing them of the location of the agency. The advertising and marketing side is reaching the largest number through social media and advertisements on public roads.

C1

A project to establish vocational courses and attract specialists in human resources

 I worked on a project while I was at the Career Center at King Saud University, which is to attract managers and specialists in the field of human resources and offer important courses for male and female students. It aims to guide them to the right path after they graduate from the university